

2 years of experience ali_navidi24@yahoo.com Portfolio: westernal.me/ Blog: dev.to/westernal westernal 🕤 ali-navidi-850a80209 🛅

westernal

ali-navidi 🖹

Junior Front-End Developer

A 22 years-old frontend developer and a recently computer (software) engineering graduate, coding since 2018 and over 2 years of experience in developing websites, trying my best to write clean code, higher up the performance and improve the user experience, always seeking to improve my abilities and learn new things.

Skills: (Next.js Node.js Express.js MongoDB React.js HTML CSS **TypeScript** Cypress SEO Git Bootstrap Svelte С JavaScript Remix Java Tailwind GraphQL Python

Experience

Restarone Solutions Inc. restarone.com

Sep 2022 to Dec 2022

Frontend Engineer Toronto, Canada

- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment.
- Standardized all output with a new, responsive, mobile-first approach and strategy.
- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility.
- Following SEO best practices.
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments.
- Fixing bugs and testing for usability.
- Creating tools that improve site interaction regardless of the browser.

Oben Origin co. Jan 2020 to Nov 2021

Frontend developer Tehran, Iran

- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment.
- $\hbox{-} Standardized all output with a new, responsive, mobile-first approach and strategy.}\\$
- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility.
- Following SEO best practices.
- Collaborated with product team members to implement new feature developments.
- Fixing bugs and testing for usability.
- Creating tools that improve site interaction regardless of the browser.

Projects

social-media-frontend

Westernal: a full stack social media based on songs

JavaScript, CSS, Cypress, Next.js

social-media-backend

Westernal: a full stack social media

 ${\sf JavaScript}, {\sf Node.js}, {\sf Express.js}, {\sf MongoDB}$

Cinema

github.com/westernal/Cinema

Watching and downloading movies website and progressive web app (PWA) with Next.JS and TypeScript

Type Script, Java Script, CSS, Next. js

sari-sartel

sari-sartel.com/ github.com/westernal/sari-sartel

Sari-sartel: a mobile and accessories shop.

CSS, JavaScript, Next.js

Dashboard

 \oplus dashoard.vercel.app/ \bigcirc github.com/westernal/Dashoard

Admin dashboard using Next JS

JavaScript, CSS, Next.js

Education

Noshiravni University of Technology nit.ac.ir

Bachelor's of Science, Computer Engineering

Oct 2018 to Feb 2023

Publications

DEV Community

How do you write your CSS?

DEV Community

Languages

(Farsi Native

English Advanced